#### Contact

415-525-1028 (Mobile) anthonybruer@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/anthony-bruer-rn-bsn-ccrn-cmc-294731120 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Nursing
Healthcare
Medicine

Languages

English

# Anthony Bruer, RN, BSN, CCRN-CMC

ICU Travel Nurse at TotalMed, Inc.

San Francisco Bay Area

# Summary

Experienced, and certified Critical-Care Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & healthcare industry. Skilled in Healthcare Information Technology (HIT), Electronic Medical Record (EMR), Cardiac/Medical/Surgical/Neuro ICU specialties. Strong healthcare services professional with critical-care Charge Nurse experience in ICU/SCU setting. Recently transitioned to the role of Assistant Unit Manager for Intensive Care and Step-Down Care Unit. Member of the American Association of Critical-Care Nurses (AACN). Professional areas of interest include healthcare regulation/governance, quality improvement, continuing education, cost containment, Evidence-Based Practice (EBP), multidisciplinary teamwork, and nursing empowerment.

## Experience

TotalMed, Inc.
ICU Travel Nurse
April 2020 - Present (3 months)
Seton Medical Center COVID-19 RN

COVID-19 ICU RN at Seton Medical Center in Daly City, CA

MarinHealth Medical Center Assistant Unit Manager-ICU/SCU May 2019 - December 2019 (8 months) Greenbrae, California

Marin General Hospital Critical Care Registered Nurse July 2018 - May 2019 (11 months)

San Francisco Bay Area

Intensive Care Unit - Clinical Nurse II

American Association of Critical-Care Nurses (AACN)

#### Relief Charge Nurse ICU/SCU

Alameda Health System RN, BSN, CCRN-CMC, CN-II June 2016 - July 2018 (2 years 2 months) San Francisco Bay Area

Intensive Care Unit - Clinical Nurse II
American Association of Critical-Care Nurses (AACN)

BayCare Health System RN, BSN, CCRN, CN-II July 2012 - June 2016 (4 years) Tampa/St. Petersburg, Florida Area

Cardiac ICU (Oct 2012-June 2015) Medical ICU (June 2015- June 2016)

## Education

Jacksonville University

Master's Degree, Nursing Administration · (2015 - 2017)

Polk State College

Bachelor's Degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2008 - 2012)